(MELANCHOLIC MUSIC)
(FAINT VOICES)
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(TRADITIONAL MUSIC)
(FAINT VOICES)
(THE GIRL AND HER
GRANDFATHER SPEAK IN ARABIC)
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(THE GIRL SPEAKS IN ARABIC)
(FAINT VOICES)
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(MELANCHOLIC MUSIC)
(UNINTELLIGIBLE VOICES
FROM THE MOBILE HOME)
(MELANCHOLIC MUSIC)
(A DOOR OPENS)
(AMINA LAUGHS AND MARA YAWNS)
Hey, sweetie. Come here right now.
(AMINA LAUGHS WITH JOY)
- (Mara) So fancy for breakfast.
- (Joe) Amina, breakfast!
(Amina) Grandpa!
(COUGHS FROM THE KITCHEN)
(MUSIC OF "LET ME BE YOUR WHISKEY"
BY ALEXANDER LUDWIG)
(JOE IS COUGHING)
- Hey. Morning, dad.
- (singing) ..the rain...
(singing together) Let me be
your whiskey. Kill the pain.
Thank you.
(JOE MAKES A SOUND OF PAIN)
- Oh, be careful.
- Yeah, yeah.
Oh, you reunited with your best friend.
Oh... If she sets her mind in something...
Reminds me someone I know.
I don't know who that is.
(Mara) Adorable.
Mina, do you want orange juice?
(CAR HONKING)
Daddy!
- (Joe) I thought he was coming tomorrow.
- What date is it?
Jesus, it's the 23rd.
Shit!
(BIRDS SINGING)
(Mara) So, I conveniently forgot, sue me.
(Joe) You can't stop her seeing her father.
(MELANCHOLIC MUSIC)
- You're taking his side now?
- It's not about sides.
Your daughter deserves
to know her daddy.
(MELANCHOLIC MUSIC)
You know you loved each other once.
(Mara) Yeah, I wasn't
the one who ruined it.
(Mara) He was working late hours,
doing God knows what with who.
I know.
(MELANCHOLIC MUSIC)
Come here right now.
(AMINA SCREAMS WITH JOY AND LAUGHS)
(MELANCHOLIC MUSIC)
There's daddy. Okay, all right.
(Amina) Daddy!
(Karim) Hello, puppy.
(KARIM LAUGHS JOYFULLY)
(UNINTELLIGIBLE VOICES FROM KARIM)
10:00 am, as promised.
- I'll bring her back at 6:00.
- Okay. Bye, baby.
(SMACKING KISSES)
Are you okay?
You seem a little distracted.
Uhm... Yeah, yeah,
I'm fine. Just work stuff.
(Karim) I'm good.
Okay.
(Karim) Watch your hands, Amina.
(Mara) Hey, what you got there?
(Mara) What's this?
(Mara) Should we have a story?
You want a story? Yeah.
(MELANCHOLIC MUSIC)
(Mara) Riky and Raky's adventure
began at the zoo.
(Amina) Dinosaurs live in the zoo!
- (Mara) In our story, they do.
- (Amina) Yes!
(MELANCHOLIC MUSIC)
- (Mara) Do you like your new costume?
- Yes, Mama!
Yes!
(Mara) Now, what are we missing?
(Mara) Drugs! For papa, of course.
(MARA AND AMINA LAUGH)
- (Mara) That's not what we pay.
- But it is what your father's medication costs.
That may be. But I've never paid
that before. I have all the records here.
(from the loudspeaker) Today's
special discount...
...customers can get 20% off,
please take your coupon to the checkout.
- (Mara) Can I just see the manager?
- (Pharmacy manager) I am the manager, Ma'am.
(Mara) What happened to Frank?
(Pharmacy manager) He retired last week.
Moved to Boca with his family.
- (Pharmacy manager) Just give me a minute.
- (Mara) Yeah.
Oh! Okay, I think I see what's going on.
(Pharmacy manager) You are right.
We just update some details.
I'm so sorry about that, Ma'am.
- You can go and pay at the cashier up front.
- Thank you.
Mina?
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(Mara) Amina?
(Mara) Mina?
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
Amina?!
MINA!
Has anyone seen my daughter?
She's dressed as a dinosaur...
(Security guard, muffled voice) Ma'am,
I need you to step outside the store...
(muffled voice) Have you seen her?
Is she here? Fuck!
Mina! Have you seen a little girl? She's
only four! Please, God, please, help me!
(Mara, crying) Oh, my God! Please!
(MARA CRIES OUT LOUD)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
- Did you find them? Where are they?
- Give them a chance. What's going on?
We're doing everything
we can to find Amina.
I know Karim took her.
I know he did.
He was acting real fucking weird yesterday.
And then Mina told me he was
talking about me to someone on the phone.
- He's threatened it before.
- He has.
If that's the case,
we're struggling to understand...
...why Karim didn't just keep Amina
on one of his visits.
How am I supposed to know that?
Can you think of anything
you may have done?
- Something I may have done?
- Goddamn' it. This ain't her fault.
(Male detective) I didn't mean that.
She didn't do anything to cause this.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
(MARA CRIES)
I think he's gonna take her home.
Home?
- Syria.
- (Joe) Syria.
He used to talk about it all the time.
(Mara) Getting a job
at a hospital near his family.
(Mara) We got divorced,
he tried to do it then,
I had to get a restraining order,
to stop him taking her out of the country.
You need to check all the airports.
What? What is it?
There isn't a federal law that
prevents a parent taking their child...
It's kidnapping. He's kidnapped her.
...their own child internationally.
(Female detective) If that's the case,
I'm sorry, there's nothing we can do.
You've gotta be kidding?
He can just... He can just take her?
So I just... I just...
I lose my daughter?
(Male detective) We're following
all the procedures...
...we have roadblocks in places...
(THE VOICE DISSOLVES)
What other possibilities? What?
You mean like a child-snatcher?
Yes, could you tell me which Ohio airport
I'd need for a flight to Syria?
- (Female operator) Hold, please.
- (Mara) Ah-ah.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(Mara) You can't hide from me. I see you.
- (Amina) Ah!
- (Mara) There she is!
(Female operator) Flights to Syria depart
from Port Columbus via Amsterdam
and rage from $750 to $1000.
(Mara) Okay, thank you.
We went to Karim's house.
I'm afraid it was cleared out.
(Male detective) There were
just a few things left.
Did you check Port Columbus airport?
We found his car in long-term storage.
(Male detective) We're checking flight lists,
but we now suspect he has left the country.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(Mara) Karim Saleh Taleb.
(Joe) She doesn't have
any contacts for his family.
- (Mara) Radiology.
- (Female operator) Sorry, I don't understand.
He said his father lived in Riyadh, in Saudi
Arabia, but there's no record of him being there.
(Joe) Look, she never went there
and they never came here!
(Female operator) Sorry,
I don't have anyone by that name.
- Okay.
- (Joe) I don't know.
You're the lawyer, don't you
have an investigator or something?
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(Joe) I don't like your
attitude either, pal!
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(Joe) Oh, God...
(SOUND OF A GUN LOADING AND THEN A SHOT)
(GUNSHOT)
(MUSIC FROM THE RADIO STOPS)
(DOG BARKING OUTSIDE)
(SAD MUSIC)
(NON AUDIBLE CRYING)
(MARA CRIES DESPERATELY)
(SAD MUSIC)
When Karim took Amina overseas,
it wasn't a crime, if you can believe that.
I've been without my baby girl for...
...(crying) over two years.
(MELANCHOLIC MUSIC)
And every day I don't get to see her...
...it hurts like a bullet.
Thanks to your incredible generosity...
...I'm gonna get to go to Washington.
And I'm gonna knock on every door
and talk to every suit.
(Mara) And do everything
I can to find my baby.
I won't rest until I bring her home,
where she belongs.
(Mara) My mum left me when I was little,
I am not walking away from my own.
(PEOPLE CLAP AND CHEER MARA)
(MELANCHOLIC MUSIC)
(DOG WHINING)
(JOE COUGHS)
- I'm afraid to leave you.
- (coughing) No, stop right there.
You stick to your guns.
Just like I taught you. Yeah.
(JOE INHALES AND EXHALES DEEPLY)
- I love you.
(MARA SNIFFLES)
(EPIC MUSIC)
(FAINT VOICES)
Take it.
- State your intent.
- (Mara) Petition for a Senate resolution.
And the support of your governor,
then bring it back.
You can't block the door, Ma'am.
Excuse me, I can stand here,
it's my First Amendment right!
An appointment will be sent to you
within the next six months.
Six months? I think I'll wait.
Ma'am...
(MELANCHOLIC MUSIC)
Do you speak English?
I can't read the signature on my x-ray.
The majority of kidnappings
in this country are committed by parents.
I think it says Karim Taleb.
Last year, over 25 thousand children were
abducted by parents and nothing is being done!
(Female operator) There's no position here
by that name.
Okay. Thanks anyway.
(MELANCHOLIC MUSIC)
(ANCHORMAN, ON TV) Mara Danning has returned
to Washington to action a hunger strike...
...with the parent's
protest group she formed...
...in the wake of the disappearance
of her daughter, four years ago.
(MELANCHOLIC MUSIC)
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(WIND BLOWING)
(Robeson) Mind if I sit?
(MARA SIGHS)
- Can I help you with something?
- (Robeson) No.
(Robeson) But I might be able to help you.
Look, cowboy,
I just want to be alone, okay?
(Robeson) I'm in the
child recovery business.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
You did this?
Is it legal?
As legal as abduction.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
I'm broke, so...
I know.
Keep that.
(Robeson) I have a proposition for you.
Come work for me.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(Robeson) You help me
find other people's kids.
I'll help you find yours.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
You know, it pays pretty good too.
(Robeson) Call me.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
Mara, this is Carl. Heads up linguistics,
pretty much anything I can't do.
He's my second-in-command.
- I'm your only-in-command...
- (Robeson) Right.
- Nice to meet you.
- Glad you called.
It's not a yes.
Okay.
It's for you.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
Hey. This is a good thing.
(Robeson) I have contacts all over
the Middle East. We'll find her. In time.
(Mara) I haven't seen my daughter
in four years, 86 days, four hours...
- (Carl) How long has it been since you've eaten?
- (Mara) Nine days.
(Carl) Here.
(Mara) I can't.
(Robeson) We're your best option, Mara.
(MARA COUGHS AND THEN THROWS UP)
(Carl) You alright?
(Robeson) Here.
(Mara) I don't understand why you want me.
I trained as a seamstress.
(Robeson) Well, if I can
be completely honest...
...we need a woman in our team.
(Robeson) You rouse less suspicion
in this line of work.
(Carl) And you're tough.
(Robeson) That should get you started.
Enough to help with your dad's treatments.
Are you ready for your first case?
Come with me.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(Robeson) This... This is Maya.
That's her son, JD.
(Robeson) Barely sees the father until one day
he decides: "You know what? I want my kid back".
(Robeson) He beats her senseless
and then takes the kid back to Mexico.
(Robeson) I need more
intel. She's holding back.
Figure she's scared.
Well, of course she's scared. Look at
you. You're like a goddamn sack of rocks.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
No one knows what this feels like
more than you, Mara.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
He said you could get him back. Is it true?
Please. I just want him with me.
(crying) I can't sleep. I can't breathe.
We will try to get him back.
First, could you just tell me
a little bit about your son?
(MAYA SIGHS)
He is gentle, you know.
He can spend hours drawing and...
(MAYA SIGHS)
...he really likes animals.
(MELANCHOLIC MUSIC)
- What part do I play?
- Your job is to keep the child calm.
(Robeson) At least until we can hand him
back to the client.
You give us plausibility,
keep everything looking normal.
- So I'm playing mother.
- (Robeson) Exactly.
Let me run you through
the plan, step by step.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(Robeson) Finding and recovering
the target is hard enough.
Then you get him across
the border with fake paperwork.
- How do we do that?
- This is only Mexico to Arizona. It's easy.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(TOLLING BELLS)
(Robeson) A lot of stray dogs in Mexico.
(FAINT VOICES)
(CHILDREN CRYING)
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
Hey...
(UNINTELLIGIBLE DIALOGUE)
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(Robeson) Okay, we're on. Let's go.
Keep a lookout.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
Shit...
We're in.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
Oh, oh. Hey, wait.
- Shit!
- What?
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
Class must have cancelled. Move it.
(FAINT VOICES)
(Carl) Damn! We missed our window.
(Robeson) Means we're
going to have to improvise.
(DOG BARKING)
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
- Hey, get ready.
- We can't do it here, can we?
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(DOG BARKING)
(FAINT VOICES)
(Carl) Hey.
(DOG BARKING)
(Carl) Wanna play with her?
(FAINT VOICES)
(ROBESON WHISTLES)
(Carl) What is that?
(DOG BARKING AND JD LAUGHING)
(JD) Oh! No, no!
(Robeson) Take him! Take him!
(UNINTELLIGIBLE WORDS BY JD)
(UNINTELLIGIBLE WORDS BY JD, MARA SIGHS)
(SUSPENSE MUSIC AND CRYING)
You do it! Go, Go!
(UNINTELLIGIBLE WORDS BY JD)
(Robeson) Come on, go! Go!
Come with me, it's okay! Come on!
(Carl) Hey. What the fuck you looking at?
Get out of here.
(FIGHTING SOUNDS)
I'm not going to hurt you, okay?
I'm taking you home to see your mom.
Mama. Would you like that?
Good boy. Hold my hand.
(FIGHTING SOUNDS AND UNINTELLIGIBLE VOICES)
(FIGHTING SOUNDS AND SCREAMS)
(FIGHTING SOUNDS)
(ROBESON SCREAMS WITH PAIN)
Shit!
(AGITATED MUSIC)
(THE WOMAN SCREAMS)
(Mara) Oh, sorry!
Mara! Mara. Hey.
(THE WOMAN MAKES ANGRY SOUNDS)
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(Robeson) This way. This way!
(JD'S FATHER IS SPEAKING IN SPANISH)
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(Carl) Here! Come on.
Move, move, move, come on!
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(Robeson) Come on! Go, go, go!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(JD'S FATHER IS SPEAKING IN SPANISH)
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(MARA GASPS FOR BREATH)
Hey, we just...
All right. Good boy.
(SOUND OF A CAR APPROACHING)
(Robeson) All right, she's here.
Keep him here.
Once we're paid, we'll bring her in.
Are you fucking serious?
Business first.
Two more minutes, I promise, alright?
- (Maya) Thank you for your time.
- (Robeson) Of course.
- (Maya) May I go?
- (Robeson) He is waiting for you.
(Maya) Thank you.
Oh, my God. Oh! Oh, my God!
(Maya, crying) Oh, my God!
(CHEERFUL MUSIC)
(Maya, crying) Oh! Oh!
(MAYA AND JD CRY)
(MELANCHOLIC MUSIC)
(Robeson) Can I have
what she's having, please?
(Robeson) Hey.
(Robeson) How you doing'?
(ROBESON SIGHS WITH RELIEF)
(Robeson) Your cut.
- (Robeson) Thank you.
- Wow. That's...
That's more than I make in six months.
Oh, that's just a fraction
of what I need for Amina.
We did something good here.
You know that, right?
So how come I feel like a mercenary?
We have to be paid
for the risks we take.
She was desperate.
(Robeson) But she found the money.
And that's good, right?
I could never afford that.
You won't have to.
(Mara) Right. "Quid pro quo".
It's the jobs they'll pay for it.
Eventually.
How long's eventually?
Sometimes it's cut and dry.
You know, you find the kid, you find
a way in. It's pretty straightforward.
But not mine, right? Not Amina.
Well, your ex is pretty good
at covering his tracks, but you know that.
(Robeson) I mean, you've been
looking for him a lot longer than I have.
You don't have kids of your own, right?
- (Robeson) No.
- So...
Why do you do it?
(ROBESON SIGHS)
Well, I've just gotten out of the Marines.
Panama City Beach.
Was pretty down and out.
Didn't have a lot of transferable skills.
(Robeson) And I was hanging at the
vet center, you know, looking for work.
(Robeson) Then one
day, this guy comes in...
...and he's talking about this Washington
mom who wanted her kid snatched back.
(Robeson) You know, it
was really good money.
Turns out...
I was pretty good at it.
You know, gave me purpose.
So then I don't know,
formed the unit, hired Carl.
Rest is history.
You ever had a job go bad?
Let's not dwell on that. Okay?
Today was a good day.
To your future.
(FAST-PACED MUSIC)
(Carl) Scotland?
(Robeson) The kid's grandmother gave
evidence that the stepfather is violent.
Yeah, he has convictions...
...but he won't be in Edinburgh when we
snatch back, he'll be traveling for work.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(AIRPORT OF PARIS-LE BOURGET)
Okay.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(MUSIC FADES)
- (Female operator) May I help you?
- (Mara) Yeah. Hi.
Could you tell me who I need to speak to
get a list of all the hospitals in Lebanon?
We have a new case. Top priority.
Albania!
Thought it was getting
pretty rough out there. It's in chaos.
Yeah, well, chaos is good cover.
- Where's the rest of the intel?
- That's all I have.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(Robeson) It's got to be this one.
(UNINTELLIGIBLE VOICES OF THE CHILDREN)
There.
(Robeson) Mara, grab her. Come on.
Aria?
- (Mara) Come with me, sweetheart.
- (Carl) Come on. Come on. Come on.
(Robeson) Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
- (Robeson) Stay close.
- (Carl) Let's go.
(Robeson) This way. This way!
(Robeson) Hey, hey, get the fuck back!
(THE MAN SPEAKS IN ALBANIAN)
(A WOMAN SPEAKS IN ALBANIAN)
(FIGHTING SOUNDS)
(Robeson) Get off her! Hey! Get out!
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
- (Robeson) Hey! Get the fuck out!
- (Carl) Go, go, go!
(SOMEONE SPEAKS IN ALBANIAN)
(Carl) Against the wall.
(FIGHTING SOUNDS)
(Robeson) Come on, Let's go.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
- (Carl) Let's go.
- (Robeson) Come on.
(SOUNDS OF PAIN)
- (Robeson) Come on, come on.
- (Carl) Come on.
- (Mara) Come on, come on.
- (Robeson) Come on.
(Robeson) Hey, we got to get to the car.
(Robeson) Go, go, go.
(A MAN SPEAKS IN ALBANIAN)
(Robeson) Hey, back. Back.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Stay back!
(FIGHTING SOUNDS)
- (WOMAN) Go, go!
- (Robeson) Stay back!
(FIGHTING SOUNDS)
(GUNSHOT)
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
- (Mara) Don't fucking touch me.
- (Robeson) Hey!
Hey! Mara!
(GUNSHOTS)
Come on, run! We got to go. Go!
- (Carl) Go, go, go, go!
- Go, go!
(POLICE SIRENS)
(Robeson) Fuck!
Where's the transport?
- (Carl) Mitch?
- He pulled the plane.
(Carl) Who?
Lewis.
This is CIA?
Why the fuck didn't you tell us?
CIA? What? Who's Lewis?
- (Robeson) Hey. It was on a need to know basis.
- (Carl) Need to...
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
- I'm your partner! I'm in need to know!
Stop it. What does this mean?
It means the CIA got us to do a dirty job and now
that it's gone wrong, they're leaving us in it.
Is that true? They're not going to help us?
I'll figure it out.
- I thought we worked for parents.
- We do.
It's still a father getting back his
daughter, who pays us doesn't matter.
Doesn't matter?
What... what we do, who we
do it for is all the fucking matters.
Get us the fuck out of here.
(MELANCHOLIC MUSIC)
(JOE, on the phone) I hope you know
what you're doing.
(Mara) I'm helping people
get their kids back.
(JOE) And is this the best way
to get Amina back?
(Joe) Because you're just putting so much
trust in this thing. I just worry that...
...you've lost track
of where you're trying to get to.
Listen, I'll decide who or what I trust.
(Mara) I have to go. Love you.
(Mara) Then 500 feet
and the venue is on the left.
At least I think, it's a little unclear.
- Yeah, Carl's out taking photos.
- Okay.
(Mara) Main entrance is on the main road.
But there's another way on the corner
that takes us to the kitchen.
- What?
- You're kind of a natural at this.
What if we're giving
her to the wrong parent?
What if the mother is no good?
Where's this going?
I almost got rid of her.
Amina.
(Mara) And now I can't
bear to live without her.
I met Karim in the hospital, I had all
these problems with my hands and feet.
He did all my scans.
(Mara) We started
seeing each other after that.
(Mara) He was kind and
funny and took care of me.
Made me feel safe.
I never intended to get pregnant.
I freaked out.
(Mara) I left Karim a message,
and I drove myself to the clinic.
Right when I was about to sign the papers,
Karim came rushing in...
...just... full of passion.
That's what he was like
about the things that he loves.
He said: "We can do
this. It's going to be okay".
And it was. For a while.
Then he started acting really weird,
staying out late.
Wanted me to quit my job.
I started drinking too much, I guess.
I mean, it's not really your fault.
You didn't really know the guy.
How do you know
what I should be punishing myself for?
Okay.
Here's what I do know.
Parents, they need you on these jobs.
(ROMANTIC MUSIC)
What about you?
Do you need me?
(ROMANTIC MUSIC)
(SOUNDS OF KISSING)
(SAD MUSIC)
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
Robeson.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
What have you got?
- What about Romania?
- I'm working on it.
Petra's father really
wants his daughter back.
She's the most important thing
in the world to him.
(Lewis) I don't object to your private cases, but
not at the expense of what the CIA needs from you.
Okay, well, I think
I'm helping these parents, too.
And I'm sure that they are very grateful.
But you're a military man,
so I know that you understand...
...the plight of housewives and
grandparents is not quite as vital...
...as keeping this country
and its assets safe.
Stop deprioritizing my cases,
Mitchell, or you won't have any.
(Robeson) All right, I'll move
Romania to the top of the list.
- (Lewis) How're things going with Danning?
- (Robeson) Good.
- (Lewis) She's still looking for her kid.
- (Robeson) Of course.
(Lewis) Just remember to keep
the trail cold for as long as possible.
Why would you say that?
Karim Taleb is a dangerous man.
(Lewis) She's better
off without him in her life.
How dangerous, Lewis?
That's classified.
You do your job and I'll do mine.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
- Hi. Do you speak English?
- (Female operator) Yes, ma'am.
Thank you. Ehm...
(Mara) I have a patient at your hospital,
but I can't read his chart.
I can only read the
name of the radiologist.
Can I speak to him, please?
His name's Karim Taleb.
- (Female operator) One minute, please.
- Mm-mm.
(Female operator) He is not working today.
Would you like to leave him a message?
- Taleb?
- (Female operator) Yes.
(Mara) T-A-L-E-B.
(Mara) He does?
That's him?
That's him!
- What? Amina?
- (crying) My God.
(CHEERFUL MUSIC)
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(SOUND OF THE DOORBELL)
(SOUND OF A DOOR OPENING)
(Mara) Come on.
(SOUNDS OF POLICE SIRENS)
(SMACKING KISS)
- (Robeson) Mm...
- Mitchell.
- (Robeson) Mm-mm?
I found him. Karim is in Lebanon.
(Robeson) How did you?
I tracked him down
to a hospital just outside Beirut.
He's been working there for a whole year.
- Are you sure?
- Oh, Jesus Christ, Mitch.
Do you know how many calls I've made to
hospitals in Syria and surrounding countries?
Hundreds. And suddenly,
just like that, there he fucking is.
He didn't even change his name.
Oh, so that's what this is.
You come over. Use me.
(Mara) No. This is the
best lead I've ever had.
- I just want to get out there.
- What am I always telling you?
- You have to stop and think!
- Don't fucking yell at me.
This is finally something real for me.
Okay. I'm sorry. I didn't...
You're right.
It's a good lead.
But you won't go out there on your own.
(Robeson) So when the time is right, we'll do
it like all the others. Planned. Rehearsed.
And when will be the right time, Mitch?
Because you keep saying that.
The fucking time is now.
We need to get out there.
Is the Beirut job still on the table?
No. The Beirut job is too risky.
So you take it, and then the client will pay
for you to pull strings to get us out there.
Please.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
So, as far as we can
tell, exit points are here.
And the rear trade entrance. That'll be
our best bet to avoid our private security.
Right. Well, we only have one
invite, so it will have to be me.
You get trapped,
you have to fight your way out alone.
- Yeah. I've done it before.
- No.
- I don't like it.
- What?
You're kidding, right? It's the perfect setup
and the biggest score we've ever gotten.
You know Lebanon is still unstable, right?
Beirut is militarized, and these people
have money for private guards.
I'm the one that has to get us out if all
goes to shit. Nah, this is a no go for me.
No. I may never have
another chance to get out there.
- We'll find another way.
- It's been eight years. Eight fucking years!
How much more time
do you think I can wait?
(Robeson) Jesus Christ.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
- What the fuck was that?
- I told you.
I don't like it. It feels dangerous.
More dangerous than taking kids
from rich-as-fuck statesmen?
Maybe she's better off
if she lets this whole Lebanon lead go.
Are you serious?
She's done all those jobs with us
because you made her a promise...
...that one of them would be her own kid.
Imagine that, Mitch,
having a mother who loved you that much.
I sure as shit wouldn't have ended up here.
Come on, man.
Help us figure out the snatch.
Then we'll go out there,
do it as well as we usually do it...
...and then afterwards
we'll help her get her daughter back.
(Carl) Okay?
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
Come on, man, fuckin' do this.
(Robeson) Okay.
- (Robeson) We're good.
- What?
You better know this house inside and out.
Every room, every exit.
And this one's by the book.
My rules. Okay?
(Mara) Yeah.
(Robeson) Yeah.
(Mara) Thank you.
(Robeson) Okay.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
It's for you.
(HEAVY BREATHING)
(Joe) I've waited
as long as I could for Amina.
When your mom left, remember?
I didn't know...
...whether either of us would be okay.
(Joe) You were so tiny. Remember?
(Joe) I took you to the park.
You climbed a jungle gym and you fell off.
I bashed my teeth.
(Joe, whining) And that woman,
she came...
...rushing over.
(Joe) She said: "Where is your mother?"
And you said...
"My mom's gone.
But my dad's here and we're just fine."
(JOE SIGHS)
That's when I knew
you would always be okay.
- You have to be strong for me.
- (crying) No.
(crying) Dad, please, no.
You tell her I love her so much.
(JOE BREATHS HEAVILY)
(crying) Hey, dad, dad...
I need to rest now.
(SAD MUSIC)
(Mara) Yeah.
(MARA CRIES AND JOE BREATHS HEAVILY)
(SAD MUSIC)
(SOUNDS OF THE PLANE LEAVING)
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(FAINT VOICES)
(ORIENTAL MUSIC)
(UNINTELLIGIBLE VOICES IN ARABIC)
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(SOUND OF A DOOR OPENING)
You okay?
Hi! Mama!
- Who are you and what did you do with Soraya?
- Hey!
You're so tall.
Get over here. Your mom's here?
Yeah.
(Dasia) Oh!
(A MAN AND DASIA SPEAK IN ARABIC)
(Robeson) It's so good to see you.
- Oh, long time.
- Too long, Dasia.
- This is Mara.
- (Dasia) Hi. - Hi.
Soraya, go and get the tea. Please.
(Robeson) Nothing changed around here.
(Dasia) No, it's like a zoo in here
sometimes. I hope you don't mind.
- But you'll be sleeping in the living room.
- Oh, no.
I didn't want you
to have to share with the men.
That's very thoughtful. Thank you.
Come on.
(Dasia) Robeson told me that your ex-husband
is living here. You are okay to talk about it?
Yeah, of course.
- For you.
- Oh, thank you. Thank you.
Please.
- (Mara) She's wonderful.
- (Dasia) They grow so fast.
Do you know where your ex works?
At a hospital just outside the city, I
think. But I don't know where he lives.
I'll take you there tomorrow.
See if we can find out.
(TRAFFIC SOUNDS)
(CHEERFUL MUSIC)
Hey.
(Mara) I think I might finally be under
the same little patch of stars that she is.
(CHEERFUL MUSIC)
I know you feel close to her.
I really need you focused
on this job first. Okay?
I know.
(CHEERFUL MUSIC)
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(UNINTELLIGIBLE VOICES)
He was on a temporary contract.
He's not here anymore.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
Hey. It's a process.
He's in the city.
We're going to find him.
(ROCK MUSIC)
- Can you move in it?
- Think so.
Yeah.
(Robeson) Okay. No heroics tonight.
(Robeson) Grab the kid
and you get out of there.
(Robeson) Be careful, Mara.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(FAINT VOICES)
(THE BODYGUARD SPEAKS IN ARABIC)
Thank you.
(FAINT VOICES AND MUSIC)
(Isra) As-salam alaykom.
Wa Alykom As-slam.
- Are you from the embassy?
- Oh, God, no. Fuck politics. I'm in finance.
(Isra) Oh, excellent.
Please do tell me if you need
an introduction to any of my other guests.
That is so kind of you.
In the meantime, could you point me
the direction of the ladies room?
- It's down the hall.
- Thank you. Oh!
Shukran jaziilan.
(FAINT VOICES)
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(VOICES FROM A TV)
(VOICES FROM THE TV)
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(SOME PEOPLE SPEAK IN ARABIC)
(Mara) Come on. There's a good girl.
Okay, let's go. Come on.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
It's gonna be okay.
(VOICES IN ARABIC FROM THE KITCHEN)
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
What are you doing with my daughter?
- I'm not going to hurt her.
- You're taking her away from me?
(SALMA WHINES)
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(Mara) Don't.
Salma, come.
(GUNSHOTS)
(SALMA SCREAMS)
(SOUNDS OF PAIN)
Salma.
- (Isra) Oh...
- Oh my God.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
Is that her?
- You okay?
- Drive!
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(THE GUARDS SPEAK IN ARABIC)
(Carl) I see 'em, hang on.
(Mara) I got you, baby.
(THE MEN SPEAK IN ARABIC)
(Robeson) Get down!
(GUNSHOTS)
(Robeson) Keep your heads down!
(Robeson) One way. Watch out! Shit.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
What happened in there?
(Robeson) Mara, are you going to tell us?
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(Mara) That's a good girl.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
Alright...
That's a good girl.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
Okay, it's okay.
(SOUND OF A CAR APPROACHING)
(Robeson) He's here.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(SALMA SPEAKS IN ARABIC)
(Robeson) Of course.
(THE MAN SAYS SOMETHING IN ARABIC)
(MAN) Thank you so much.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(WATER RUNNING IN THE SHOWER)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(SOUND OF THE DOOR OPENING)
(WATER RUNNING IN THE SHOWER)
It was an accident, Mara.
You're not going to let me look
for Amina anymore, are you?
(WATER RUNNING IN THE SHOWER)
(Robeson) Okay, I'm going out.
See if I can find us a way home.
- I'll come.
- (Robeson) No.
It's not safe. Stay here at the hotel. At least
until I can find out if we're in the clear.
(SOUND OF THE DOOR OPENING AND CLOSING)
(FAINT VOICES)
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(Carl) Who is it?
- (Dasia) Dasia.
- It's Dasia.
- (Dasia) Dasia!
- Okay, okay, okay. Hey.
- Hey.
- (Carl) Hey.
- You shouldn't be here.
- I have a lead.
On what?
On Amina.
- (Carl) No. No. Wait for Robeson.
- (Mara) We have to go.
No. You know, a lead
only lasts so long. I'll go by myself.
- No. You heard what he said.
- A couple of hours, tops.
Then at least we'll have some intel.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
Shit.
(FAINT VOICES)
(Dasia) You should wait here.
- In and out. Okay?
- (Dasia) Yeah. Okay.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(Robeson) What are you doing out here?
This is my territory.
(Lewis) The more pertinent question is:...
...what the hell are you doing out here
and not in Romania, like I ordered you to?
And at the center of all this is Denning...
...who's compromised us with a snatch back
caught up in a bloodbath.
(Lewis) A woman who shouldn't be
anywhere near here...
...but is at risk of destroying everything
that I've worked for the last eight years.
And a woman who's the only one
who could've gotten us in and out.
- Is that right?
- (Robeson) That's right.
And you're telling me
that you had to take a job in Beirut?
She goes to school
with her youngest granddaughter.
(Mara) Where? Have you met her? Amina.
(Dasia, in Arabic) Have you met Amina?
(Grandmother, in Arabic) Once.
She is... Rather a rebel, I think.
Once. She thinks that
Amina is rather a rebel.
Is she? That's good.
(DASIA SAYS SOMETHING IN ARABIC)
(Mara) What time do the schools finish?
- At 3:00 p.m...
- Okay, could she give me an address?
Robeson, let me make it absolutely clear to
you, as you don't seem to have got the message.
It is imperative to my interests
and therefore to yours...
...that she does not find Karim Taleb.
So when you asked me
to stop looking into Karim, I did.
But if you expect me to keep that mother
from her daughter...
...you better tell me
what the fuck's really going on right now.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
How much do you know
about your husband's life here?
What do you know
I mean, nothing. Why?
(Dasia, in Arabic) Why do you ask?
- (in Arabic) - It's late. I should go.
- Why? Wait.
She should leave.
(in Arabic) Wait. Give
her the address. Please?
- (in Arabic) I can't.
- (Mara) Please, please. As a mother.
(in Arabic) As a mother, I tell you
to go see your daughter.
See that she is well, but
then you should leave.
As a mother she tells you: Go see your daughter,
see that she is fine. But then you should leave.
(Grandmother) The enemy
of my enemy is my friend.
(Grandmother) Good luck.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
Listen. I cannot come to the school. I cannot
bring trouble to my family. Do you understand?
Of course. Of course.
You've done more to help me in a few days
than anyone in my own country did for years.
Go.
- (Robeson) You had me lie to her.
- No.
It's not lying if you
didn't have all the facts.
- (Lewis) Oh!
- Fuck you.
I tipped you off to her...
...so you could give her an opportunity
to get involved in something, right?
- Distract her.
- Something that would give her life purpose.
- And then you let her lead you right here.
- You used me.
You need to convince her
that the leads she has are false...
...and you need to get her
out of the country immediately.
And if I don't?
Then I can't guarantee
that she or her family will be safe.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
- From you.
- From anybody.
Her desperation is making the situation
unstable. And that's when people get hurt.
Do you really want that
on your conscience?
I need you to serve your country right now,
not her. I know you understand that.
And never put your hands
on me like that again.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
It's it.
It looks pretty secure.
Heavy gates, guards, CCTV.
No back entrance.
School got out 10 minutes ago.
So she lives?
- Hey.
- What?
(FAINT VOICES)
(Carl) Is that her?
(CHEERFUL MUSIC)
(NON AUDIBLE DIALOGUES)
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
Hey, hey, hey! They'll see you.
Shut the door.
We have no plan. Anything you do now,
we just tip them off and ruin everything.
Hide your face.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(FAINT VOICES)
No! Hey! Hey! Fuck.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(FAINT VOICES AND TRADITIONAL MUSIC)
(FAINT VOICES)
(KARIM, AMINA
AND HER GRANDFATHER TALK IN ARABIC)
(FAINT VOICES)
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(NON AUDIBLE DIALOGUES)
(AMINA AND HER GRANDFATHER TALK IN ARABIC)
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(NON AUDIBLE DIALOGUES)
(AMINA AND HER GRANDFATHER TALK IN ARABIC)
(FAINT VOICES)
(UNINTELLIGIBLE DIALOGUE)
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(AMINA AND THE MAN SPEAK IN ARABIC)
(KARIN, HIS FATHER AND
THE MAN SPEAK IN ARABIC)
(Karim) Amina! Amina!
(AMINA CRIES OUT LOUD)
What the fuck have you done?
Take her. Just take her to the car.
(Karim) Amina!
(AMINA SCREAMS)
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
Be careful! Be careful!
- Try to keep her calm. Try to keep her calm.
- Go, go, go, go!
- (AMINA CRIES AND SCREAMS)
- Come on!
(SOUND OF THE ENGINE THAT DOESN'T START)
- Hey, Mara, Come on!
- It's okay. It's okay.
Nobody's going to hurt you, okay?
- (Mara) Amina...
- Fuck. Come on.
(AMINA SAYS SOMETHING IN ARABIC)
- What does that mean? Carl!
- I don't know. I don't know!
Amina!
(Mara) What are you doing, Carl?
- (Mara) Carl, go!
- (Carl) Okay.
(Carl) Come on, Come on, come on.
Damn it, come on!
(Carl) Fuck! Here we go, here we go.
(TIRES SCREECHING AND AMINA CRYING)
No, no!
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
- No, no, no. She cannot be here.
- No, no, no, no, let us in, let us in, let us in.
Just until we figure this mess out.
It's all right. Does she speak English?
I don't know if she speaks English.
(SOUNDS OF ANGER)
Amina?
Tell her I love her.
(Mara) And tell her she should never
have been brought to this country.
And I didn't know
and I couldn't find her.
And I just... I just want to take her back
to America...
...to be her mom, to be your mom.
She is your mother.
She is your mother, Amina.
I don't have a mother.
My mother is dead.
What?
She said: "I don't have a mother.
My mother is dead".
(AMINA CRIES DESPERATELY)
(DASIA SPEAKS IN ARABIC AND AMINA CRES)
(Robeson) What's going on?
- What the fuck!
- It's not how it looks.
- Really?
- We had to grab her. We had no other choice.
(AMINA CRIES)
We can't stay here.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
- Amina. Amina, you have to come with me.
- No!
(DASIA SPEAKS IN ARABIC)
(AMINA CRIES)
Take this.
You should have known better.
It was the wrong way.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(BIRDS SINGING
AND VOICES FROM THE OUTSIDE)
So, ehm... Carl just told me
you speak good English.
You're stubborn, huh?
I guess you got
something from me after all.
Maybe he's wrong.
Maybe you don't speak.
I'm top of my class in English.
You were always super smart, Mina.
Amina.
Amina, sorry.
Ehm... I have carried this
every day since you left.
Also...
(Mara) This is me and you.
(Mara) You're four, it's your birthday.
You're much older now.
Do you have any hobbies?
You still like swimming?
- We have a pool.
- Wow. Huh? You do?
I race on the team.
I'm... How do you say?
- Oh, Captain?
- Captain.
Wow.
You know, I was the one
who taught you how to swim.
At home, at the lake,
with your grandpa.
I have my "jaddy" here.
Your "jaddy", that's what you call?
Where is he?
Oh... He died.
He'd been sick for a long time...
...but he wanted me to tell you
that he loved you...
...very, very much.
(Robeson) You should have waited.
I'm done waiting, dummy.
I saw an opportunity and I took it.
- You're reckless.
- I'm her mother.
I saw her, you know?
After all this time.
(whining) I'd imagined it for so long.
(whining) My heart, Mitchell.
I couldn't wait
Mitchell, it's me. I imagined her
running into my harms.
But now she's looking at me
like I'm a fucking monster.
How do we get out of this country?
We have to take Amina back to Karim.
- Is that a joke?
- I can't get her out.
We're all in danger if we don't return her.
Why? What's happened?
You have to trust me.
- Oh, what? Trust you?
- Yes.
After I finally do the thing
that no one was prepared to help me with...
...you're telling me to take her back?
What the fuck is going on?
If you try to get past me, I will kill you. If
you play one finger on her, I will fuck you up.
- Stop! Stop!
- Tell me what's going... Tell me!
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
Karim has ties to Muslim Brotherhood.
(Robeson) There, now you know.
What?
Apparently, he got caught up
to his family's connections.
They blackmailed him
into laundering money for them.
And that's when the CIA discovered him.
Oh, the CIA knew?
Mara, we're hired contractors.
My contact, Louis, told me Karim
cut a deal with the CIA as an informant.
He works for them.
In return, he gets to keep Amina.
(Robeson) He's been
relocating them out here.
(Robeson) Sorry. I just found this out.
All those dead ends.
He blocked my search in Washington,
and hired you to keep me from her.
Yes.
Okay. Muslim Brotherhood.
I thought he was having affairs.
If we don't get you out
and return her...
...I honestly don't know what he might do.
(Mara, crying out loud) Oh! Oh!
- Please, stop...
- (Mara) OH!
You kept me working for you.
You slept with me.
I'm sorry, okay?
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
So what are you going to do now, Mitch?
Because I am not giving her back.
And we both know it.
So either help me or let me go.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
When this is over,
I never want to hear from you again.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(AMINA SIGHS)
You're ready?
(BARKING OF A DOG)
(BARKING DOGS)
Here. Keep your faces covered.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(FAINT NOISES)
(Mara) Where are we?
We need to stop for papers
so we can get across the border.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
Thanks for being so quick. I owe
you. I'll call you when I get to Damascus.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(Amina) Is he your husband?
No.
Would he be with us in America?
No, we just...
We just work together, that's all.
(Mara) Hey, do you want a swing?
(Mara) Come on.
It's okay. You on?
- Mm-mm.
- All right, I got you.
Okay. Are you ready? One, two, three.
(CHEERFUL MUSIC)
(MARA LAUGHS)
(MARA AND AMINA LAUGH)
(CHEERFUL MUSIC)
(JOE AND AMINA LAUGH)
(AMINA LAUGH)
(CHEERFUL MUSIC)
(MARA AND AMINA LAUGH)
I have something similar.
(CHEERFUL MUSIC)
(UNINTELLIGIBLE DIALOGUES IN ARABIC)
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
Passport.
(BANGS)
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
There are Americans here.
They want to see your papers.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
Shit.
Fuck.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(Amina) What is happening?
- We can find another route.
- It will be like this everywhere.
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(Border guard) Going somewhere?
(Border guard) Go, go. "Yalla"!
(Border guard) Are you American?
(Border guard) Are you
traveling with anyone?
Wait. Damn, what are you doing?
What's best for us, Mitch.
It's okay, come on, sweetie.
Mara...
Say whatever you need to say
to keep us safe. I'm not losing her again.
- Hey!
- Go, Amina.
(FIGHTING SOUNDS AND SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(GUNSHOT AND FIGHTING SOUNDS)
Don't move!
Put the gun down!
(SOUNDS OF PAIN)
Go! Go when you have the chance! Go!
(FIGHTING SOUNDS)
(SUSPENSE MUSIC)
(Amina) Where are we going now?
I'm going to find us somewhere to cross.
It will be okay.
I'm hungry.
Here.
I only eat vegetables.
I don't have anything else.
- I want to go home now.
- I told you.
We are going home.
Not to America.
I like it here.
I like my friends and my house.
Listen.
You're going to make
so many new friends in America.
"Jaddy" won't be there.
- Well, no...
- (Amina) Who will be?
Me, Mina.
Amina.
(whining) Amina.
You and me.
I don't want to be with you.
Okay, well, you don't mean that.
I want to stay with baba.
Why would you take me away from him?
Hey! Sit down.
Sorry. I didn't mean
to hurt you. Are you okay?
It's just...
(crying) You don't know
how hard it's been.
And...
...how long it has taken me to find you.
But I was never lost.
What?
I was just at home.
I never asked you
to come and find me.
(SAD MUSIC)
- (Amina) Where are you going?
- (Mara) It's okay, I'm just... Wait there.
(SAD MUSIC)
(WHISTLING WIND)
(SOUND OF THE COUCH STOPPING)
(SAD MUSIC)
(WHISTLING WIND)
Where is she?
She's safe.
- Who's she with?
- A friend.
- I need to see her. Now.
- Yeah, it hurts, doesn't it?
Eight years of hurt.
- How could you do it?
- (Karim) I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for what I've
done to you, everything.
I swear, Mara. I was... I was cornered.
(Karim) If I stayed, I would have put
both of you in danger.
And now she's been protected
by a very powerful organization.
Yeah. Who helped you to kidnap her.
Do you understand how crazy that sounds?
The people I work for threatened me
and the family if I didn't relocate...
...I couldn't face it without her.
And honestly, I wanted
to give her a better life.
As long as I kept quiet and played
by the rules, they gave us that.
You stole her from me.
My little girl.
Our little girl.
(GUNSHOT)
Don't you fucking come near me.
(WHISTLING WIND)
Sorry. Okay?
(SOUNDS OF FEAR)
(KARIM SNIFFS)
(MARA EXHALES)
(MARA GASPS FOR BREATH)
Did you know I was looking for you?
They kept telling me
you were getting on with your life.
And you believed that?
It was easier that way.
You took my most...
...precious thing I've ever had.
(crying) You obliterated my life.
And you spent this whole time
telling her that I was dead.
I don't... I don't get
how you can hate me that much.
- I don't. I don't hate you. I thought...
- (Mara) Shut up!
I don't give a fuck of
what you think, Karim.
I swear to God, if you say
another fucking word, I will kill you.
(Mara) You have no idea.
(WHISTLING WIND)
(SAD MUSIC)
But she's not the little
girl that I lost anymore.
(SAD MUSIC)
(crying) She doesn't know me.
So I guess...
...I kind of am dead, aren't I?
Thanks to you.
(WHISTLING WIND)
(MARA CRIES SILENTLY AND DESPERATELY)
Promise me she'll be safe with you.
(SAD MUSIC)
Promise me!
I promise.
She's safe.
She's happy.
She has a good life here.
(Karim) You're seeing it for yourself.
(crying) Was it ever real? You and me?
Yes. I loved you, Mara.
(Karim, whining) I did.
(MARA SIGHS)
All right, so you're going
to tell Amina the truth.
(Mara) You're going to tell her
that it was your fault...
...if she hasn't had a mother
to be there for her this whole time.
You're going to tell her everything
that I did to try to find her.
(Mara) You're going to
beg for her forgiveness...
...and then you're going to help us
rebuild our lives together, okay?
(KARIM SNIFFS)
I will.
This is not for you.
This is for her.
I understand what my daughter needs.
I always have.
(KARIM GASPS FOR BREATH)
(SAD MUSIC)
Amina, it's okay, I promise.
Hey.
(SAD MUSIC)
Remember:...
...I've always loved you.
(SAD MUSIC)
(KARIM LAUGHS)
- (Karim) Amina!
- (Amina) Baba!
(SAD MUSIC)
(AMINA AND KARIM CRY)
(KARIM SNIFFS)
(SAD MUSIC)
(SMACK OF A KISS)
(MARA CRIES)
(SAD MUSIC)